

Tatjana Nikolic **Personal details**

Date of birth: 18.10.1992.

Address:

Koste Abrasevica 13, Cicevac 37 210 Serbia

Contact

Phone:

+381631660746

Email:

tatjananikoli@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/tatjana-nikolica74b23226

Languages

English					
Spanish					

Hobbies

- Theater
- Handicrafts
- Fixing things

Summary

A driven young woman, who enjoys working in a team and inspiring others to reach their full potential. Open minded and welcoming of new experiences and new people. Confident in self and respectful to others. Effective at decision making and well versed in dealing with dificult situations.

Education

High School of Economics Kruševac

2007-2011

Economic technician

Faculty of Philology and Arts, University of Kragujevac

2011-present

Serbian language and literature

Experience

Mega taxi, Kragujevac Taxi Displatcher

Dec 2015 - May 2016

Sputnik 1957, Kragujevac

Bartender/ waitress

Aug 2018 - Dec 2018

Tango caffe, Kragujevac

Bartender/ waitress

Dec 2018 - Sep 2019

Milky Pancakes, Kragujevac

Nov 2019 – Oct 2020

Milky Pancakes, Zlatibor

Oct 2020 - May 2021

Milky Creperie & Café, Vrnjacka Banja

May 2021 - June 2022

Personal assistant, Swiss Onz GmbH Feb 2023 – present

Volunteer experience

SKC Kragujevac

2017 – present

Actress

Red Cross Ćićevac

2003 - 2014

- Human Values Promotion Coordinator
- President of the Youth Field Unit
- Peer Ecuador / Advisor
- Health education and AIDS education
- International humanitarian law education
- Human trafficking education

Radio Ćićevac

2006 - 2011

Radio Show - Neki novi klinci

Editor and Presenter

Certifications

Agile humans

Agile humans Certificate Practitioner